Also using media, to keep this layer thinner.
We're going to be bring this down and around the fingers here and what we're really doing is establishing tone.
The actual colors are going to be darker than this but I greatly prefer putting some of the darker elements, over the lighter ones, in this case with clothing.
Another thing is, we are going to have the collars, and everything here, be blue but they're going to be some black regions, in the middle here.
So get a second flat brush, flat head here and some black and we'll start putting this on, in here.
Lots of medium, very very thin coat here.
Very thin.
Some white's going to also be injected, to get some gray tones going on, especially towards the top here.
This is going to make the clothing a little more interesting.
This is actually, somewhat, of what our subject's wearing too.
Keep in mind, the first layer is going to be the closest to our portrait, before we then veer off into some interesting alternative directions.